Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, we're waiting
where we should be going, go?
That's right. We're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride
away, we're all together as well.
So let's just stay with the sun,
while our dreams are never ending.
So let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake
up, heartbeat, we will be one, go ahead.
My darkness will swallow the
world, just you wait and see.
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates
Roger's treasure belongs to me
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther.
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow we
will find suspense And then commence to
Live out another day so intense.
That's right, we're shining,
Running forever. Let's go along
with curiosity. Our feelings lead.
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever. Open the map inside your
heart and see. No matter where we end up,
our mods will never give up There's a fire
in our dreams And you can never, never,
never, never stop it We
will be one, go ahead!
Ricky lands a clean hit on
the mighty Kiros! Actually,
this is the first time anyone has landed a
Clean hit on Kiros. In
his entire tenure here!
And it's over!
Kyrus continues his streak!
Three thousand battles and three
thousand victories over nine years!
He's a living legend!
You might even say the word invincible
was invented to describe this man!
Damn it.
You're the leader of this kingdom.
Rick, why?
I became quite strong after
training with you, didn't I?
But you lowered your guard as
soon as you noticed it was me.
You're not such a beast after all.
You've punished yourself enough.
It's already been nine years.
Nearly a decade of your life
locked away in this cage.
There's something important I
need you to do on the outside.
Kiros, rather than regretting the
lives that you took in the past,
you should devote yourself to
saving lives in the future.
I think you can find meaning in that.
Yes, sir.
We're counting on you, Kiros! Kiros!
Thanks for all your hard work!
Kiros, protect me!
We love you!
Captain Kiros, so popular with the ladies.
But I haven't forgotten
that you're a killer.
Honestly, Father shouldn't
allow you inside the palace.
I object to it.
Please, Princess Scarlet.
That's cool.
Stop it digging up his old drama.
The captain of the guard is supposed to
be a symbol of righteousness, not this.
Scarlet.
Even if you can fool the rest of
the kingdom, you'll never fool me.
You'll show your true color soon enough.
Don't you dare lay a
finger on me or my sister.
You keep your distance, understand?
Huh, I don't know.
He's not like that. Stop it.
You shouldn't look.
His mind's probably filthy.
But my job is to protect you.
No thanks.
Lady Scarlet has been kidnapped!
Curse those pirates!
What happened to her bodyguards?
All defeated! No way!
What do we do?
Forgive me for touching you.
I know you told me not to.
Kiros, I was so scared.
Forgive me! Forgive me!
I can't believe Scarlet is cooking.
I wonder what's gotten into her.
What did you say?
You want to resign as the royal bodyguard?
Don't tell me you've fallen
in love with Princess Scarlet.
With a beautiful princess like her?
No, I could never.
The people would certainly
celebrate such a union.
In private, at least.
But because of your past,
it would be condemned.
I'm certain of it. We are royalty.
That is how it is.
I don't care father if I can't marry
him I would rather die understand
Taken from us so yeah, I
hear it was a sudden illness.
She would have become a fine queen someday
Scarlet, as of today, you are no
longer a member of the royal family.
Officially, you are not even
alive anymore. Thank you.
I fear I failed to repay your kindness.
You most certainly have, you lout.
But I'm more than happy to forgive you.
My boy, you've lived an amazing life.
Her name is Rebekah.
Kiros, she's your child.
Hold her.
I shouldn't touch such an innocent thing.
Not with these tainted hands.
It's not right.
Your father's a strange man. Sorry.
You're such a little angel, aren't you?
I'll watch over you.
I'll always be at your side.
Hurrah!
Your grandpa is here.
Yay, Grandpa!
You've gotten as tall
as my palace, Rebecca.
Father, you can take off the disguise.
Kiros, gloves first. Gloves first.
My little girl, you're so cute.
Stop crying.
The royal palace, it's on fire.
What's going on?
Our kingdom's falling apart.
I'm going to the palace.
Scarlet, Rebecca, I need you
to stay safe. Okay, Daddy.
If it gets too dangerous here, leave.
Wait for me and the red flower field.
I swear I'll come back safe.
They've got me.
You filthy pirate.
What did you do? Let him go!
Rick here was the one
burning the kingdom down.
It wasn't me.
The king would never do such a thing.
Kiros!
I don't have any Devil Fruit powers.
Remove these shackles from me.
Listen, Kiros, I've heard
good things about you.
Why not swear fealty to me?
The Rick bloodline will be
wiped out in no time at all.
And before you ask, that includes
your dear wife and daughter as well.
I've already sent men to dispatch them.
Now you'll want to watch carefully.
You're witnessing history.
The final moments of the Rick dynasty.
Crazy bastard cut off his own leg.
Kirosu no!
That little guy's fast!
He made up of the old king!
This can't be real.
What happened?
I turned into a toy?
Sorry.
I fear that name doesn't ring a bell.
Regardless, I'll never
forget what you did for me.
To a soldier.
Wait for me right where I told you.
Nobody knows my name—did the
whole kingdom forget about me I?
Have
to get to the red flower field. Scarlett.
Scarlett.
It.
can't be!
be
Someone's been shot!
Is it Riku's army again?
Dammit!
Why did you wait for me?
Why are you here?
I see now.
It seems I've been erased
from everyone's memories.
Our promises.
Our time together.
Scarlet!
Don't die!
Hang on!
Can you hear me?
Please, say something!
I'll protect you! Say it with me!
I have a favor to ask of you, stranger.
Ranger, my daughter is hungry,
and she's waiting for me.
Please.
It's Kieros.
I'm your husband.
I beg you.
Scarlet.
user
Scarlet!
How did it come to this?
I've lost her.
She's gone.
This is hell.
These useless tin arms of mine.
I can't even feel your
warmth one last time.
Scarlet!
Soldier.
Soldier!
Are you all right?
Yes, it's nothing.
You having a bad dream or what?
Listen, we have a problem.
There are enemies on their way.
Unforgivable.
How dare he pretend to
be the young master?
Straw Hat and his friends must
have made it past the second floor.
Violet's blood was on the wall.
It's no good.
At this rate, we'll be
completely surrounded.
Is it better to make a surprise
attack on Doflamingo now?
Usaland and the others must have failed.
I was wondering, Straw Hat, are
all of your friends pirates?
I realize that Franky and New Zealand are.
That a problem for you?
No, I'm a criminal myself.
I'm just grateful that
we share a common goal.
Those cracks in the ceiling
are freaking me out.
That's what happens when
you have hundreds of
powerful fighters all
competing in the same event.
It's no surprise that the
structure has taken so much damage.
That Burgess guy's out of control.
He's gonna bring the place
crashing down and suck wave
Cut that out, stop shooting us.
You're funny.
If you don't believe me,
I'll tell you again, Rebecca.
I'm the one who shot and
killed your mother Scarlet.
I would have killed you, too.
My barrier only protects against
physical attacks, not verbal ones.
Soldier... I...
I can't do it.
I'm so hungry.
Mother, I'm starving.
I'm going to bring us something to eat.
Really?
I'm too angry to even move.
Cyborg Freaky's down.
I think we're done here.
Usopp, I'm counting on you, bro.
I know you're going to start
that riot any second now.
You've got this.
Usopp, go!
They're going nuts at the executive tower.
He said his name was
Usopp of the Straw Hats?
Good luck.
I don't even know what you look like,
but I'm cheering for you, Usopp.
He'll be my hero forever if you win.
You can do it.
Being a toy is awful.
If you can fix this, I promise I'll
give up my grudge against Straw Hat.
Deal.
I'll be your flunky or whatever you want.
Just get this done.
You can have all of my money.
No price is too great!
Hey, Treble, bring sugar to
the palace and make it quick.
Take it easy, Toffee.
They tried to pull something, but
I've got it all under control now.
Uzzelad, wake up!
Why don't you take this
poison grape of yours back?
That's our only hope!
Lutata babasco grape!
It's better if you eat it.
Drop dead, will you?
Oh
I'm dead, Sugar.
Everything's alright.
Please don't pass out on me, okay?
Look!
Hustle, I did it!
Sugar passed out!
He did it!
They're growing big!
Some of them are growing really big!
I'm back!
Kinder, hey! Wake up! Hey!
It's a human!
Something's happening! What?
Those toys are acting rather strangely.
My body!
Who are you?
What's happening to me?
I'm human now!
I need that!
Don't be!
I'm sorry!
I goofed!
I goofed, Rupert!
You're trouble!
It's holding down!
Did something happen to Sugar? She...
she...
she passed out!
She got scared of pizza!
Hey, this is supposed to
be some kind of a joke.
The slaves we've been
collecting for a whole
ten years are all turning back to normal.
The Hobby Hobby Fruits
powers are wearing off.
I remember now.
What's going on?
The toys in the Coliseum are...
What's going on here?
Look at the toys!
They're turning into humans!
Also animals, apparently!
They got her. Sugar!
We worked a whole decade
enslaving all of them!
Must have found Sugar and given
her a trouncing, huh? Pathetic.
That miserable pipsqueak.
But still, I sure hope she wasn't hurt.
Aw, you care about her, don't you?
Ellis, please answer!
Sir, all of these emergency
reports keep piling up!
We've got a different
way to that step here!
The toys working at the port
suddenly turned into pirates!
Hey, this is Carter here.
The toys, they turned into
dress-wasted soldiers!
They turned into government officials,
marines, and foreign royalty!
Wild animals!
They're in the Primalist district!
I can't help!
Hang in there.
Usaland!
Me and everyone else, we all
became human again thanks to you!
You did it, Usaland!
Operation SOP is a success thanks to you!
All the people you saved,
they're smiling and cheering.
What's wrong, Winpoko?
Mom, my toy is acting real weird.
What?
Winpoko? Hold on.
Are you...
But how?
My darling, is that you?
I turned back.
Honey!
Dad, you're not Wapol!
That's right, finally! Daddy!
I don't understand.
Why have we forgotten
about you all this time?
That's how the power works.
I thought I'd be a toy forever.
Hey, Daddy, can you lift me
up high? Uh-huh. Like this?
Damn it!
Gone quiet on me again?
Where'd you run off to, you stone bastard?
Come look!
I'm not dead yet.
Our hero's alive after all!
He's scared me.
Thanks, Usalind!
I never stop believing in you!
Everything went according to plan.
Just so cool!
And don't worry, you can
leave the rest to my friends.
The real battle has just begun.
Okay!
Rise up!
Take down Doflamingo!
I can't believe that Rotten King
tricked us for all these years!
You've lost it.
He's a fine leader.
We only thought that
because he heard the truth.
He's really...
a demon.
I'll have your head, Doflamingo!
Get out here and fight!
I've got ten years of suffering
I need to pay you back for!
Hey, Isha, any clue what's happening?
It would appear that
the tides have turned.
Despite all appearances,
there is a deep darkness here,
much deeper than I had anticipated.
Go to hell, Doflamingo!
Who's the cape guy?
Kaidou, it's you! Huh?
Even I lost my memories of him.
I don't get it.
What do you mean?
Hey, where's the soldier?
That man is him.
How's that work?
Originally, the toys were human like us.
When they changed, they were
erased from our memories.
The girl who did this
sugar passed out just now.
So our memories all came flooding back.
He's the former captain of
King Riku's army, Karoo!
The strongest gladiator in
the history of the Coliseum!
Wait, the guy they have the statue of?
Yes, but more than that, he's my
brother-in-law, Rebecca's father!
But she said she didn't know that guy!
Once our memories are lost, they can't
be regained till Sugar is stopped.
Even so, he's watched over his
daughter for the past ten years.
Even though he was only
a toy soldier to her,
he stayed by her side every day,
protecting her the best he could.
Hey, who goes there?
It's you, Karoo, my boy. Sir!
I'm sorry to keep you waiting
these ten long years, King Rick.
But now, I'm here to save you!
We shall reclaim this
kingdom at long last!
Ten years.
For ten long years, we've suffered.
Hmm.
Toe Flamingo!
Yog-master!
You've been dead!
Mingo just died!
Well, that sucks.
I was gonna be the one to kick his ass.
There they are!
I see ya!
Get there!
They found us.
We've got to go save Traffy!
I don't even know how to explain this!
It's inconceivable!
Where the hell did this
gorilla come from? Run!
I can't believe this.
Shrebel.
Left sugar unguarded?
Hey, I'm not your babysitter.
Stop your bawling.
It's not like that.
I had...
I had a father.
Now that the smoke is clear, it's time
we uncover the truth, right, Rebecca?
There's a core at the heart of all things.
Once you find that...
You lost me!
You sound cool as hell, and I
still look up to you, of course.
but, uh, you lost me!
Even the ring we stand in now has a core.
I think it's about time we wrap this up.
Dragon Claw Fist?
Dragon!
Unbelievable that was a single blow
from Lucy. The ring's going under.
The whole ring has exploded.
That's great. What the hell did you do?
Got places to be?
Need to win!
What's a lot commotion up there?
Hey, Hawk.
Did he do something reckless again?
He's heading underground now.